<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AI Wallpaper Changer</string>
    <string name="app.generate.prompt">Prompt</string>
    <string name="app.generate.negative_prompt">Negative prompt</string>
    <string name="app.generate.model">Model</string>
    <string name="app.error.fetching_models_failed">Fetching the list of available models failed, please try again later.</string>
    <string name="app.generate.steps">Steps (%d)</string>
    <string name="app.generate.preview">Preview</string>
    <string name="app.error.generating_failed">Generating your image failed, please try again later.</string>
    <string name="app.error.create_tmp_file">Could not create a temporary file to store the generated image in.</string>
    <string name="app.preview.description">Here you can preview the generated image. If it looks good, you can set up automatic wallpaper change using the prompt and other parameters.</string>
    <string name="app.preview.alt_text">The AI generated image using parameters from the previous form.</string>
    <string name="app.preview.button.ok">Looks good!</string>
    <string name="app.preview.button.cancel">Try again</string>
    <string name="app.title.configure_schedule">Configure Schedule</string>
    <string name="app.schedule.times">How many times a day do you want the app to change your wallpaper?</string>
    <string name="app.schedule.schedule_button">Schedule!</string>
    <string name="notification.channel.background_work.id" translatable="false">background_work</string>
    <string name="notification.channel.background_work.title">Background work</string>
    <string name="notification.channel.background_work.description">This channel is used to display a notification while the app is generating a new wallpaper in the background. Without this we cannot ensure that the wallpaper will be generated successfully.</string>
    <string name="app.error.notification_permission">We need the notification permission to run a job in the background.</string>
    <string name="app.success.scheduled">Success! Your wallpaper should now be changed at the specified interval.</string>
    <string name="app.generate.cancel_schedule">Cancel existing schedule</string>
    <string name="app.succes.cancelled">The scheduled wallpaper change has been successfully cancelled.</string>
    <string name="app.generate.estimated_time">Estimated wait time: %ss</string>
    <string name="app.generate.estimated_time.too_long">We\'re still working on it.</string>
    <string name="app.generate.estimated_time.pre_start">We\'ll get to generating your image soon.</string>
    <string name="app.generate.last_generated">Wallpaper last changed: %s</string>
    <string name="app.generate.advanced_toggle">Advanced</string>
    <string name="app.generate.sampler">Sampler</string>
    <string name="app.generate.clip_skip">CLIP skip (%d)</string>
    <string name="app.generate.width_and_height">Width and height</string>
    <string name="app.generate.width">Width</string>
    <string name="app.generate.height">Height</string>
    <string name="app.generate.upscaler">Upscaler</string>
    <string name="app.select.empty_option">-- none --</string>
    <string name="app.title.history">History</string>
    <string name="app.history.no_history">There is no wallpaper history, go on and generate some wallpapers!</string>
    <string name="app.history.open_in_browser">Open in HordeNG</string>
    <string name="app.generate.nsfw">NSFW enabled</string>
    <string name="app.title.settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="app.settings.api_key">Custom API key</string>
    <string name="app.settings.api_key_hint">Leave empty to use the default. Or <a href="https://aihorde.net/">create a free account</a>.</string>
    <string name="app.error.invalid_api_key">The provided API key is not valid.</string>
    <string name="app.error.forbidden_request">Generating your image failed. Perhaps your request is too complex?</string>
    <string name="app.title.premium">Premium</string>
    <string name="app.premium.description">Opting for the Premium subscription allows you to jump ahead in the line, much like a custom API key with high kudos amount does.\n\nWhat essentially happens is this: instead of being grouped with the default, anonymous API key users, you join a higher tier with a considerable amount of kudos, thereby gaining queue priority.\n\nThe benefits of this include:\n- High priority in the queue (equivalent to providing your own api key with high amount of kudos)\n- The ability to set more complex generation parameters (as is possible with any API key, even without kudos)\n- Your support contributes directly to the continuing development of the app\n\nPlease note that the premium subscription doesn\'t provide:\n- Exclusive access to special features\n- Improved image quality above what is usual without a premium subscription\n\nSimply put, a Premium package isn\'t necessary unless you want faster response times during peak hours. If you still decide to subscribe, knowing these conditions, we sincerely appreciate it!</string>
    <string name="app.premium.unavailable">Premium is not available in your country.</string>
    <string name="app.premium.billing_unavailable">Billing is unavailable on your device, cannot purchase Premium.</string>
    <string name="app.premium.already_purchased">You have already purchased Premium, thank you!</string>
    <string name="app.premium.activate">Activate Premium</string>
    <string name="app.premium.error_launching_subscribe">There was an error while trying to launch a payment window, please try again later.</string>
    <string name="app.title.help">Help</string>
    <string name="app.help.prompt_description">Prompt describes what you want to see in the image. Use keywords separated by comma. For example, to get an abstract image of a woman, you can use: woman, abstract, art, colorful. The prompt can also contain parameters, more on that below.</string>
    <string name="app.help.negative_prompt_description">Negative prompt describes what you don\'t want to see in the image. The format is the same as in Prompt, to complement the prompt example, you might add \"realistic, ugly, deformed\" as a negative prompt to ensure you get some nice abstract image. The prompt can also contain parameters, more on that below.</string>
    <string name="app.help.model_description">Model determines what the image will look like. Each model has different style and the only way to know what you like is to either try it out or search for the model on the internet. Some good starting models include: Lyriel (for artistic images), I Can\'t Believe It\'s Not Photography (realistic images), AlbedoBase XL (general model that has no specialization)</string>
    <string name="app.help.sampler_description">Sampler is what\'s responsible for the technical process of generating an image. There\'s not really a universal sampler that\'s best in all cases, you might want to experiment a bit. If you don\'t want to, k_dpmpp_sde or k_dpmpp_2m is a good start.</string>
    <string name="app.help.steps">Steps</string>
    <string name="app.help.steps_description">Each step the image is generated based on your prompt and the image generated in previous step, meaning after each step the AI tries to make the image more like what you describe in your prompt. Note that it will eventually go overboard and make the image worse than the previous one, that\'s why more steps doesn\'t necessarily mean better. The sweet spot is usually between 20 and 60.</string>
    <string name="app.help.clip_skip">CLIP skip</string>
    <string name="app.help.clip_skip_description">CLIP is a neural network that\'s in charge of converting your prompt from text to a numerical representation that the image generator then understands. The neural network is made of layers and this setting allows you to skip some of them and feed the numerical representation of your prompt to the image generating process earlier. In simple terms, this changes how the AI sees your prompt without actually changing the prompt. Vastly different results might be produced depending on the model and the value you set here. Usually 1 or 2 is a good value, but feel free to experiment.</string>
    <string name="app.help.width_height_description">Width and height, perhaps unsurprisingly, control the dimensions of your image. All values must be divisible by 64. Note that most models are either trained on 512x512 or 1024x1024 images, so any other dimension might have some caveats. Generally speaking, both dimensions should be 1024 or less if you want consistently good resulst. Going above 2048 rarely makes sense and the pool of workers able to take on your request goes down with higher resolutions. Feel free to experiment to see which dimensions look good. Note that the values here are not necessarily the target dimensions, as an Upscaler that makes the image larger can be used afterwards. In fact, the default values calculate the ratio between your width and height and set the larger side to 1024, afterwards an upscaler is used to enlarge the image either 2x or 4x based on your resolution.</string>
    <string name="app.help.upscaler_description">Upscaler is a model that enlarges your image after it has been generated. Every Upscaler uses a different algorithm to do so, so the resulting image might look slightly differently, try out which one looks the best for you. If you specify an Upscaler, your image is first generated at the resolution you specify and afterwards enlarged by your selected Upscaler. By default, either RealESRGAN_x4plus or RealESRGAN_x2plus is used depending on your resolution.</string>
    <string name="app.title.about">About</string>
    <string name="app.about.text">The app uses <a href="https://aihorde.net/">AI Horde</a> to generate images.\n\nYou can contact the author on the following social media:\n\n- <a href="https://lemmings.world/u/rikudou">Lemmy</a>\n- <a href="https://phpc.social/@chrastecky">Mastodon</a>\n- <a href="https://matrix.to/#/@rikudou:lemmings.world">Matrix</a>\n</string>
    <string name="app.about.version">Version: %s</string>
    <string name="app.settings.save_wallpapers">Save all wallpapers in a directory</string>
    <string name="app.generate.cfg_scale">CFG scale (%.1f)</string>
    <string name="app.generate.hires_fix">HiRes Fix</string>
    <string name="app.shortcut.next_image">Next wallpaper</string>
    <string name="app.shortcut.next_image.info">The next image using the stored parameters will be generated soon.</string>
    <string name="app.shortcut.next_image.error">There is no schedule set, cannot generate next image.</string>
    <string name="app.about.share_logs">Send logs to developer</string>
    <string name="app.about.share_logs.no_log_file">There is no log file to share with the developer.</string>
    <string name="app.about.share_logs.chooser_title">Share logs with developer</string>
    <string name="app.title.uncaught_exception">Unhandled error</string>
    <string name="app.uncaught_exception.explanation">There was an error which we forgot to handle. It has been logged and if you want to help out, you can go to the About page and send the logs to the developer.</string>
    <string name="app.uncaught_exception.go_to_about">Go to the About page</string>
    <string name="app.permission.data_saver.dialog.body">Your device has Data saver enabled which prevents this app to work in the background when using data. Please add this app as an exception if you want this app to work correctly.</string>
    <string name="app.permission.data_saver.dialog.title">Data Saver</string>
    <string name="app.permission.dialog.button.exception">Add an exception</string>
    <string name="app.permission.dialog.button.ignore">Ignore</string>
    <string name="app.permission.dialog.button.dont_ask_again">Don\'t ask again</string>
    <string name="app.permissions.doze_mode.dialog.body">Please add this app as an exception to the battery optimizations of your device, otherwise the app may not work as expected.</string>
    <string name="app.permissions.doze_mode.dialog.title">Ignore battery optimizations</string>
    <string name="app.generate.models.single">single model</string>
    <string name="app.generate.models.multiple">multiple models</string>
    <string name="app.title.select_models">Choose models</string>
    <string name="app.delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="app.select_models.selected">Selected models</string>
    <string name="app.select_models.all_models">Available models</string>
    <string name="app.save">Save</string>
    <string name="app.select_models.selecting_failed">Failed to save the models you selected, try again, please.</string>
    <string name="app.help.cfg_scale">CFG scale</string>
    <string name="app.help.cfg_scale_description">CFG scale controls how closely does the AI follow your prompt, the larger the value, the more it follows, at least in theory. Between 1 and 10 is usually a good value, but it really depends on the model.</string>
    <string name="app.help.cfg_hires_fix_description">HiRes fix first generates your image at a lower resolution and then upscales it. This can help when the model can\'t natively generate images at your choosen resolution. Only works for larger images, low resolution images may fail generating or the HiRes fix might be silently turned off. Exception to that rule is Stable Cascade model where HiRes fix works at all resolutions.</string>
    <string name="app.error.prompt_parameter_invalid">Cannot use the parameter ${%s}, permissions are not granted.</string>
    <string name="app.premade_prompts.failed_getting">Failed getting list of premade styles, try again later.</string>
    <string name="app.generate.select_prompt_button">Select a predefined prompt</string>
    <string name="app.title.premade_prompts">Premade prompts</string>
    <string name="app.premade_prompts.show_examples">Show examples and use style</string>
    <string name="app.parameter.season.description">Resolves to the current season, spring, summer, autumn or winter.</string>
    <string name="app.parameter.time_of_day.description">Resolves to the current time of day: morning, noon, afternoon, evening, night or midnight</string>
    <string name="app.help.prompt_parameters">Prompt parameters</string>
    <string name="app.help.prompt_parameters.description">Prompt parameters are special tokens you can use in your prompt (or negative prompt) and when you make a request, they will be replaced by their current value. All parameters start with ${ and end with }.</string>
    <string name="app.premade_prompts.use_style_button">Use style</string>
    <string name="app.premade_prompts.error_setting_prompt">Error setting the style, please try again later.</string>
    <string name="app.generate.style_successfully_set">The parameters from the style have been successfully set</string>
    <string name="app.premade_styles.downloading_failed">Downloading one or more images failed</string>
    <string name="app.parameter.dark_mode.description">Returns either dark or light depending on your system theme. Great for using with background.</string>
    <string name="app.parameter.battery.description">Resolves to either \"high\", \"medium\", \"low\" or \"very low\" based on your current batter level.</string>
    <string name="app.error.unknown_style">The provided style could not be found.</string>
    <string name="app.premade_prompt.author"><![CDATA[<b>Author</b>: %s]]></string>
    <string name="app.premade_prompt.description"><![CDATA[<b>Description</b>: %s]]></string>
    <string name="app.settings.allow_large_values">Allow large values</string>
    <string name="app.settings.allow_large_values.description">When toggled on, you can set larger values for steps, cfg scale etc. Unless you know you need it, you can safely turn this off.</string>
    <string name="app.generate.prompt_permissions">Your prompt or negative prompt uses features that require access to the following permissions:\n\n%s</string>
    <string name="app.generate.prompt_permissions.title">Permissions needed</string>
    <string name="app.error.missing_permissions">Required permissions weren\'t granted.</string>
    <string name="app.error.parameter_replacing_failed">Failed replacing parameters, try again later.</string>
    <string name="app.parameter.weather.description">Resolves to the current weather condition, like \'cloudy\', \'clear\', \'foggy\' etc. Requires access to location.</string>
    <string name="app.parameter.country.description">Returns the name of the country you\'re in based on your current location.</string>
    <string name="app.settings.custom_parameters">Custom parameters</string>
    <string name="app.custom_parameters.add">Add a parameter</string>
    <string name="app.custom_parameters.no_parameters">You don\'t have any custom parameters. Why don\'t you create one?</string>
    <string name="app.custom_parameters.create_title">Create a parameter</string>
    <string name="app.custom_parameters.edit_title">Edit a parameter</string>
    <string name="app.custom_parameters.parameter_not_found">Parameter does not exist, please restart the app.</string>
    <string name="app.custom_parameters.add.name">Parameter name</string>
    <string name="app.custom_parameters.add.description">Description (optional)</string>
    <string name="app.custom_parameters.explanation">Custom parameters make it possible to use a custom parameter based on other parameters in your prompt. Any built-in parameter can be used and arbitrary amount of if-else conditions can be used. An example of an expression is \"${bg}\" (without quotes) which can have \"dark\" or \"light\" as a value. Using if-conditions you can set your custom parameter to \"black\" if it equals \"dark\" and to \"white\" if it equals \"light\".</string>
    <string name="app.custom_parameters.edit.expression">Expression</string>
    <string name="app.custom_parameters.conditions">Conditions</string>
    <string name="app.custom_parameters.conditions.add">Add condition</string>
    <string name="app.custom_parameters.conditions.delete">Remove condition</string>
    <string name="app.custom_parameters.condition.if_equals">if expression equals this value</string>
    <string name="app.custom_parameters.condition.then">set the parameter to this value</string>
    <string name="app.custom_parameters.condition.else">if no condition matches, use this value</string>
    <string name="app.custom_parameters.no_description">No parameter description has been provided.</string>
    <string name="app.custom_parameters.edit_parameter">Edit custom parameter</string>
    <string name="app.custom_parameters.delete_parameter">Delete custom parameter</string>
    <string name="app.generic.delete_title">Are you sure?</string>
    <string name="app.generic.delete_content">When you delete this item, it\'s gone forever. Are you sure you want to do it?</string>
    <string name="app.parameter.town_description">The current town you\'re in. If it can\'t be determined, empty text is used.</string>
    <string name="app.parameter.state_description">Returns the current admin area you\'re in, for example the US state you\'re in, or generally the larger region you\'re currently in in other countries.</string>
    <string name="app.live_wallpaper.description">Have a new AI generated wallpaper multiple times a day.</string>
    <string name="app.settings.use_live_wallpaper">Use live wallpaper [experimental]</string>
    <string name="app.settings.use_live_wallpaper.description">On some devices there are problems with the wallpaper not being changed even though everything seems to work. You can check this toggle to enable live wallpaper which could mitigate the problem.</string>
    <string name="app.parameter.full_weather.description">Returns a more complex weather description like \"heavy intensity shower rain\" instead of a single keyword.</string>
    <string name="app.menu.share_current">Share current wallpaper</string>
    <string name="app.preview.share">Share</string>
    <string name="app.generate.estimated_time.pre_start.parameters">Replacing parameters in your prompt</string>
    <string name="app.error.trailing_leading_whitespace">This value contains a leading or trailing whitespace, if that\'s intentional, you can ignore this warning.</string>
    <string name="app.parameter.topography.description">Sends your location to an AI which then provides a list of few topographical tags that describe the place you\'re at. Beware that your location will be shared (anonymously) with the service running the AI model (AI Horde).</string>
    <string name="app.parameter.llm.description">Resolves to a response from a large language AI model, you have to separate your question like this: ${llm:random color}. The question can contain other parameters like this: ${llm:what\'s the capital of ${country}?}</string>
    <string name="app.parameter.temperature">Returns the current temperature in Celsius including the unit.</string>
    <string name="app.parameter.temperature_f">Returns the current temperature in Fahrenheit including the unit.</string>
    <string name="app.settings.extra_slow_workers">Allow extra slow workers</string>
    <string name="app.settings.extra_slow_workers.description">When enabled, even very slow workers are allowed to handle your requests. Note that this setting only applies for wallpapers generated in background and not for previews you\'re actively generating in app.</string>
    <string name="main.join_horde">Tip: <a href="https://aihorde.net/">Create a free account on the AI Horde</a> to get priority over anonymous users.</string>
</resources>