<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AI Wallpaper Changer</string>
    <string name="app.generate.prompt">Prompt</string>
    <string name="app.generate.negative_prompt">Negative prompt</string>
    <string name="app.generate.model">Model</string>
    <string name="app.error.fetching_models_failed">Fetching the list of available models failed, please try again later.</string>
    <string name="app.generate.steps">Steps (%d)</string>
    <string name="app.generate.preview">Preview</string>
    <string name="app.error.generating_failed">Generating your image failed, please try again later.</string>
    <string name="app.error.create_tmp_file">Could not create a temporary file to store the generated image in.</string>
    <string name="app.preview.description">Here you can preview the generated image. If it looks good, you can set up automatic wallpaper change using the prompt and other parameters.</string>
    <string name="app.preview.alt_text">The AI generated image using parameters from the previous form.</string>
    <string name="app.preview.button.ok">Looks good!</string>
    <string name="app.preview.button.cancel">Try again</string>
    <string name="app.title.configure_schedule">Configure Schedule</string>
    <string name="app.schedule.times">How many times a day do you want the app to change your wallpaper?</string>
    <string name="app.schedule.schedule_button">Schedule!</string>
    <string name="notification.channel.background_work.id" translatable="false">background_work</string>
    <string name="notification.channel.background_work.title">Background work</string>
    <string name="notification.channel.background_work.description">This channel is used to display a notification while the app is generating a new wallpaper in the background. Without this we cannot ensure that the wallpaper will be generated successfully.</string>
    <string name="notification.background_work.title">Generating new AI wallpaper</string>
    <string name="app.error.notification_permission">We need the notification permission to run a job in the background.</string>
    <string name="app.success.scheduled">Success! Your wallpaper should now be changed at the specified interval.</string>
    <string name="app.generate.cancel_schedule">Cancel existing schedule</string>
    <string name="app.succes.cancelled">The scheduled wallpaper change has been successfully cancelled.</string>
    <string name="app.generate.estimated_time">Estimated wait time: %ss</string>
    <string name="app.generate.estimated_time.too_long">We\'re still working on it.</string>
    <string name="app.generate.estimated_time.pre_start">We\'ll get to generating your image soon.</string>
    <string name="app.generate.last_generated">Wallpaper last changed: %s</string>
    <string name="app.generate.advanced_toggle">Advanced</string>
    <string name="app.generate.sampler">Sampler</string>
    <string name="app.generate.clip_skip">CLIP skip (%d)</string>
    <string name="app.generate.width_and_height">Width and height</string>
    <string name="app.generate.width">Width</string>
    <string name="app.generate.height">Height</string>
    <string name="app.generate.upscaler">Upscaler</string>
    <string name="app.select.empty_option">-- none --</string>
    <string name="notification.doze_mode.disable">Please disable battery optimizations for AI Wallpaper Changer.</string>
    <string name="app.title.history">History</string>
    <string name="app.history.no_history">There is no wallpaper history, go on and generate some wallpapers!</string>
    <string name="app.history.open_in_browser">Open in HordeNG</string>
    <string name="app.generate.nsfw">NSFW enabled</string>
    <string name="app.title.settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="app.settings.api_key">Custom API key</string>
    <string name="app.settings.api_key_hint">Leave empty to use the default</string>
    <string name="app.error.invalid_api_key">The provided API key is not valid.</string>
    <string name="app.error.forbidden_request">Generating your image failed. Perhaps your request is too complex?</string>
    <string name="app.title.premium">Premium</string>
    <string name="app.premium.description">Opting for the Premium subscription allows you to jump ahead in the line, much like a custom API key with high kudos amount does.\n\nWhat essentially happens is this: instead of being grouped with the default, anonymous API key users, you join a higher tier with a considerable amount of kudos, thereby gaining queue priority.\n\nThe benefits of this include:\n- High priority in the queue (equivalent to providing your own api key with high amount of kudos)\n- The ability to set more complex generation parameters (as is possible with any API key, even without kudos)\n- Your support contributes directly to the continuing development of the app\n\nPlease note that the premium subscription doesn\'t provide:\n- Exclusive access to special features\n- Improved image quality above what is usual without a premium subscription\n\nSimply put, a Premium package isn\'t necessary unless you want faster response times during peak hours. If you still decide to subscribe, knowing these conditions, we sincerely appreciate it!</string>
    <string name="app.premium.unavailable">Premium is not available in your country.</string>
    <string name="app.premium.billing_unavailable">Billing is unavailable on your device, cannot purchase Premium.</string>
    <string name="app.premium.already_purchased">You have already purchased Premium, thank you!</string>
    <string name="app.premium.activate">Activate Premium</string>
    <string name="app.premium.error_launching_subscribe">There was an error while trying to launch a payment window, please try again later.</string>
    <string name="app.title.help">Help</string>
    <string name="app.help.prompt_description">Prompt describes what you want to see in the image. Use keywords separated by comma. For example, to get an abstract image of a woman, you can use: woman, abstract, art, colorful</string>
    <string name="app.help.negative_prompt_description">Negative prompt describes what you don\'t want to see in the image. The format is the same as in Prompt, to complement the prompt example, you mgiht add \"realistic, ugly, deformed\" as a negative prompt to ensure you get some nice abstract image.</string>
    <string name="app.help.model_description">Model determines what the image will look like. Each model has different style and the only way to know what you like is to either try it out or search for the model on the internet. Some good starting models include: Lyriel (for artistic images), I Can\'t Believe It\'s Not Photography (realistic images), AlbedoBase XL (general model that has no specialization)</string>
</resources>